<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ministry of Agriculture of Peru</title><link>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/ministry-of-agriculture-of-peru/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/ministry-of-agriculture-of-peru/</guid><description>The Ministry of Agriculture of Peru began implementation to support for over 15,000 coffee and cacao cooperative farmers. Over a dozen independent farming organizations are joined together in a cooperative. They vote to elect representatives to operate the cooperative and make decisions on behalf of the group.
Like organizations around the world, the COVID-19 pandemic has made assembling in person much more challenging, accelerating the need to operate the business remotely.</description></item><item><title>National Cooperative Business Association (NCBA) to partner globally</title><link>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/national-cooperative-business-association-ncba-to-partner-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/national-cooperative-business-association-ncba-to-partner-globally/</guid><description>Washington DC, USA
The National Cooperative Business Association CLUSA International (NCBA CLUSA) has worked for more than 100 years to build a better world and a more inclusive economy. We engage, partner with and empower people to have a greater say in their futures and more equitable access to economic opportunities.
NCBA CLUSA speaks with a united voice before elected officials, raising awareness of the cooperative economic impact and advocating for federal policies that benefit cooperative enterprise—like access to the critical financing and technical assistance communities need to establish and grow employee-owned businesses.</description></item><item><title>Say hello to Doks 👋</title><link>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/say-hello-to-doks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/say-hello-to-doks/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DAO launches badges</title><link>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/dao-launches-badges/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://h-enk.github.io/doks-gh-pages/blog/dao-launches-badges/</guid><description>An initial set of badges are now available.
These include:
Treasurer Facilitator Lamp Lighter Moderator Badge Librarian Enroller The badge rewards vary from 0% to 5% and also vary depending on the token. For example, a Treasurer badge holder receives a 3% bonus on HYPHA payments and a Lamp Lighter receives a 5% bonus on HVOICE.
Badges will be shown on the member card.
Visit the badge library: https://dho.</description></item></channel></rss>