<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/introduction/</guid><description>Tokens Tokens represent a core component of managing your team. You configure your own token to be used for voting and financial rewards. It can be a single token, or you can create multiple tokens that are used for different purposes. To get started, we recommend a non-transferable token for voting and a transferable token for rewards.
👉 Tokens keep track of rewards and influence Roles and Projects Post roles and projects with clear descriptions so members can find work, and reward them with recurring salaries or one-time bounties.</description></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/identity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/identity/</guid><description>Modern organizations are borderless, virtual, and asynchronous. The platform features a suite of tools that allow members to know each other, if they want to.
Account names We use account names, but not just public keys.
Profiles Like all modern social platforms, we support profiles that allow members to describe themselves to the community. The platform uses blockchain authentication and encryption to secure appropriate information in a GDPR compliant manner.</description></item><item><title>Membership</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/membership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/membership/</guid><description>Flexible options allow for organizations to control membership in a number of different ways.
Single approver Single approver from a set of enrollers (see the Enroller badge) Multisig enrollers Governance vote on enrollmennt</description></item><item><title>Credentials</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/credentials/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/credentials/</guid><description>Credentials, also known as badges, are artifacts or designations that can be assigned to a member.
Similar to a role, badges are defined as an abstract document with an image, description, and optional payment coefficients. The badge is added to the &amp;lsquo;badge library&amp;rsquo; and becomes available to be assigned to individual members.
Coefficients The payment coefficients are used to juice a badge holder&amp;rsquo;s pay on both salaries and one-time payments. Coefficients are compatible with any of your token types, governance, reward, or pegs.</description></item><item><title>Governance</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/governance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/governance/</guid><description>The platform supports a wide variety of voting methods and evaluation criteria.
Voting Methods Cumulative voting Ranked choice voting Consensus voting Majority rules Super majority Variable quorum based on controversy Stake voting Elections One token, one vote One person, one vote Tokens Voting power may be set to a single token or combination of tokens.
Vote Power Decay If you select a non-transferable token to represent voting power, you may also optionally specify a decay algorithm.</description></item><item><title>Proposals</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/proposals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/proposals/</guid><description>Proposals are documents that may have special powers if and when they are passed by the organization.
The one common factor among all proposal types is that they may activate the organizational permission. This is activating full sudo permissions for the DAO.
Policy proposals Policy proposals are as it sounds. A passing policy proposal uses the organizational permission to attest, or certify, the content that is included within the proposal.</description></item><item><title>Roles</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/roles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/roles/</guid><description>Role proposals A role proposal includes the following data:
Title Description Salary amounts (per period, per token) Available dates (begin and end) Minimum commitment (e.g. no less than a 50% commitment) Available slots (1 person budgeted? or many?) When a role is approved, it becomes available for members to apply for.</description></item><item><title>Payments</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/payments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/payments/</guid><description>The platform supports endless tokenomic and payment opportunities. Here is what we have seen work the best.
Reward tokens Reward tokens are transferable, fungible tokens that are paid to donors, investors, and contributors as a reward in exchange for something of value provided to the organization.
For a reward token to be valuable, it should have a purpose. For example, an open source software team may pay their reward token to their contributors.</description></item><item><title>Accounting</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/accounting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/platform/accounting/</guid><description>The platform supports classic double-entry accounting in the same manner as many accounting packages used by businesses all over the world, including Quickbooks, NetSuite, ledger, GnuCash, and SAP.
Our implementation and support for double-entry accounting is a significant advantage when compared to other blockchain-powered organization platforms.
👉 We believe support for traditional accounting methods on blockchain is critical for higher adoption rates Double Entry Ledgers Double entry booking has been the accounting best practice used for centuries.</description></item><item><title>Data Model</title><link>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/document-graph/structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:43:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://dappdever.github.io/doks-gh-pages/docs/document-graph/structure/</guid><description>The platform stores on- and off-chain data in a flexible, content-addressed document graph.
A graph is a set of documents that are connected with labeled, directional edges.
Document A document is comprised of three primary components:
a header content - an ordered &amp;lsquo;list of labeled lists&amp;rsquo; of key-value pairs certificates Header The document header stores the following:
creator (blockchain account) created_date hash of the contents The document graph uses content-addressing, which means the unique identifier of the document is a hash of the contents.</description></item></channel></rss>